<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Personal blog</title>
    <link>https://bergmannf.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Personal blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>This is a customized copyright.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bergmannf.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying Teamspeak on a Raspberry PI kubernetes cluster</title>
      <link>https://bergmannf.github.io/posts/teamspeak-k8s-arm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bergmannf.github.io/posts/teamspeak-k8s-arm/</guid>
      <description>While this post will end up with a running Teamspeak server, it is very hard on the resources of the Raspberry Pi and might not be suitable for everyday use.
To deploy a teamspeak server on raspberry pi a few things need to be done:
 (optional) Get a Kubernetes cluster up and running (this is not required, if you just want to run the docker container directly). Get Teamspeak to run on ARM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Converting openssh private key to PEM format</title>
      <link>https://bergmannf.github.io/posts/openssh-private-key/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bergmannf.github.io/posts/openssh-private-key/</guid>
      <description>Newer version of the openssh will use their own format to store a private key:
-----BEGIN OPENSSH PRIVATE KEY----- BASE64KEYTEXT -----END OPENSSH PRIVATE KEY-----  The traditional format of the key can sometimes be useful (or even required - for example guacamole will not be able to use the OPENSSH key format).
To convert the key use ssh-keygen. The command will overwrite the private key file, so if the original key should be preserved make sure to create a backup:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://bergmannf.github.io/posts/posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bergmannf.github.io/posts/posts/</guid>
      <description>Personal blog Converting openssh private key to PEM format&amp;#xa0;&amp;#xa0;&amp;#xa0;openssh   Newer versions of the openssh will use their own format to store a private key: -----BEGIN OPENSSH PRIVATE KEY----- BASE64KEYTEXT -----END OPENSSH PRIVATE KEY-----   The traditional format of the key can sometimes be useful (or even required - for example guacamole will not be able to use the OPENSSH key format).  To convert the key use ssh-keygen.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>